{
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What do we meant by meaningful play?",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "That the rules of the game provide a fair contest"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "That there is an enjoyable outcome from the game"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "That the game has strong narrative content"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "That it is easy to link your actions to consequences"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "That the play results in meaning"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "d"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which of the following shows the difference between emergent and progression based rules?",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "Emergent rules are generated by discussions within the design team, while progression rules are determined by publishers"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "Progress rules are about scoring points, emergent rules are about developing the story"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "Progress rules are linked to events, emergent rules rely on the interaction in a simple set of rules"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "Progress rules help the player get further in the game, while emergent rules punish them to provide game balance"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "Emergent rules are created at the beginning of the design process while progress rules are a result of feedback from testing"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "c"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "A good UI?",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "Is more important in casual games than hardcore games"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "Is familiar without being boring"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "Provides all the necessary functions but no more"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "Improves the game mechanics"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "Stops being noticed"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "e"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Ludology is?",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "The study of balancing"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "The study of game design"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "The study of games"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "The study of lewd behavior in visual media"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "The study of programming"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "c"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which one of these is not a common feature of games in the RTS category:",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "Micro management"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "Strategy"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "Realtime interaction"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "Tech tree development"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "Character development"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "e"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The technical definition of feedback is",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "When the output of a system is used as part of the input in the next time interval"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "What the player sees"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "The system associated with awarding a score and accomplishments"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "The ratings provided by critics and online users rating systems"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "The responses from play-testers during the alpha and beta testing phases of game development"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which of these is not an example of negative feedback?",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "The blue shell in Mario kart"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "Rubber banding in racing car games"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "Increasing experience required to achieve higher levels"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "Enemy speed increases at higher levels"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "Spawn points that can be sniped"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "e"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "A well balanced game has which set of features?",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "No dominant strategies, large numbers of options, and many ways to win"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "Equal numbers of player and AI forces, unit strength, and asymmetric starting positions"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "Transitive unit dominance, symbolic AI, and emergent game play"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "Progression base rules, esoteric interactions, and optimal integration systems"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "Complex interactions, player feedback, and problem solving"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Strong negative feedback will",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "start players in the same place every game"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "provide better weapons as the game gets harder"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "ensures every player has the same chance of winning"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "create an unfair advantage for weak players"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "decrease the importance of the early part of a game"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "e"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "If there was another option inserted into the confidence level for this multi-choice section (current options are +1.0, -0.0 ; +1.5, -0.5 and +2.0,-2.0), which values would result in all four options remaining the best choice for at least some levels of confidence? (i.e which option would not just replace one of the current options)",
        "options": [
          {
            "key": "a",
            "text": "1.0, -0.5"
          },
          {
            "key": "b",
            "text": "1.3, -0.75"
          },
          {
            "key": "c",
            "text": "1.8, -1.0"
          },
          {
            "key": "d",
            "text": "2.0, -1.0"
          },
          {
            "key": "e",
            "text": "3.0, -1.6"
          }
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "c"
      }
    ]
  }